Guide to the WSU College of Pharmacy Records 1896-1996
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
WSU College of Pharmacy Records
1896-1996
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives and Special Collections
Archives 388
7 linear feet of shelf space 10 boxes
Records, papers, correspondence, and publications related to the Washington State University College of Pharmacy and Dean Allen I. White.
The WSU College of Pharmacy was founded in 1891, only one year after the founding of Washington State College. Programming in pharmacy was discontinued from 1892 through 1896, but has been continuously offered since. For further information, please see the written history of the College of Pharmacy in the collection’s final folder.
Professor Allen I. White served on the pharmacy faculty for 39 years (1940-1979), and served as the Dean of the college from 1960 until his 1979 1979 retirement. He passed away in December, 2002.
This collection consists of materials related to the development and management of the College of Pharmacy, including plans for buildings and remodeling, correspondence with the state Council on Postsecondary Education, College of Pharmacy publications, national accreditation documents, faculty information, budget reports, and pharmacy faculty meeting minutes.
The materials have been broken into nine series, with some series including subseries. The series, subseries, and their contents are all arranged alphabetically in a subject-based order. Series one relates to academic or educational programs. Series two relates to building construction and remodeling, some of which did not end up happening. Series three relates to the pharmacy program’s centennial. Series 4 is correspondence - the first subseries is primarily with university administrators, while the second subseries relates to legislative issues. Series 6 is evaluations of the college and its programs, including accreditation and documents relating to the State of Washington Council for Postsecondary Education. Series 7 relates to groups of specific people, primarily faculty and graduates. Series 7 is press coverage. Series 8 is various departmental reports and documents, including budgets, announcements, and student/alumni newsletters. Finally, series 9 is personal papers, documents, and publications from Allen White.
This collection is open and available for research use.
Allen I. White, an emeritus professor of Pharmacy at WSU, donated this collection to the Washington State University Libraries’ Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections (MASC) on August 22, 1996, where it was retained as UA.1996-17.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
White, Allen I. (Allen Ingolf), 1914-2002.
Washington State University. College of Pharmacy--History
Pharmacy Colleges--Washington (State)
Colleges and Universities
- Series 1: Academic Programs, 1953-1989
  - Subseries 1.1: Degrees and Courses, 1970-1989
    - Preliminary planning for Doctor of Pharmacy degree, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence related to Doctor of Pharmacy degree, 1970-1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Original proposal for Doctor of Pharmacy degree, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Proposal for Doctor of Pharmacy degree program, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Proposal for Doctor of Pharmacy degree program, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Papers and correspondence related to Doctor of Pharmacy programs, 1979-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Papers and correspondence related to revised proposal for Doctor of Pharmacy degree, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Proposal for Doctor of Pharmacy degree program, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Proposal for Doctor of Pharmacy degree program, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Proposal for Doctor of Pharmacy degree at WSU Spokane, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Proposed Pharmacology/Toxicology program - papers and correspondence, 1979-1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 1.2: Washington State postgraduate refresher course, 1962-1970
    - Proceedings of the Washington State postgraduate refresher course, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Proceedings of the Washington State postgraduate refresher course, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Proceedings of the Washington State postgraduate refresher course, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Proceedings of the Washington State postgraduate refresher course, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 1.3: Washington State Board, 1953-1981
    - Washington State Board of Pharmacy, 1978-1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Washington State board exams, 1953-1959 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Washington State board exams, 1953-1959 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Washington State board exams, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Washington State board exams, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Series 2: Buildings and Remodels, 1943-1973
  - Blueprints and sketches of proposed College of Pharmacy building (located in oversize box), 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Remodeling of College Hall - Phase 1, 1954-1960 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - College of Pharmacy remodel - correspondence, work papers, and preliminary plans - Phase 1, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - College of Pharmacy remodel - correspondence, work papers, and preliminary plans - Phase 1, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - College of Pharmacy remodel - correspondence, work papers, and preliminary plans - Phase 1, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Architectural blueprints for the proposed pharmacy building by Stanley A. Smith, 1943-1944 (Box O.S., Folder 26)
  - Architectural sketches and floorplans of a building for the School of Pharmacy and Department of Police Science by John W. Maloney, 1944 (Box O.S., Folder 26)
  - College of Pharmacy remodel - program of requirements, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Remodeling of College Hall - Phase 2, 1966-1973 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - College of Pharmacy remodel - correspondence, work papers, and plans - Phase 2, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Remodeling of College Hall - plans - Phase 2, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Remodeling of College Hall - correspondence - Phase 2, 1966-1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Remodeling of College Hall - Space Priorities Committee correspondence - Phase 2, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Series 3: Centennial of the College of Pharmacy, 1985-1992
  - College of Pharmacy Centennial - early correspondence, 1985-1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Centennial Celebration Committee, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - College of Pharmacy draft and related papers, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Centennial announcements and newsletters, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Centennial celebration photos, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Centennial celebration, skit photos, and negatives, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Series 4: Correspondence, 1960-1986
  - Subseries 4.1: Administrative, 1960-1986
    - Correspondence between College of Pharmacy and University President, 1960-1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Academic Deans' Council: Memo re UP - Academic duties, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence with Executive VP Beasley, 1967-1978 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence with Deans and Vice Presidents of Academic Affairs, 1960-1970 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous interdepartmental memos, 1968-1986 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 4.2: Legislative, 1960-1979
    - Correspondence related to U.S. Health Manpower legislation, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence related to U.S. Health Manpower legislation, 1971-1979 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence related to U.S. Health Manpower legislation, 1960-1969 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence related to U.S. legislation, 1960-1974 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence related to Washington State legislation, 1961-1971 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Comprehensive Health Planning Council of Pullman/Whitman County - meeting minutes and reports, 1968-1975 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Comprehensive Health Planning Council of Pullman/Whitman County - correspondence, meeting minutes, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Comprehensive Health Planning Council - review of relations of WSU to hospital, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Comprehensive Health Planning Council - Inland Washington Health Systems Agency, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Comprehensive Health Planning Council - Inland Washington Health Systems Agency, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - WSU Health Sciences Administration Council, 1971-1976 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - WSU Health Sciences Administration Council, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - WSU Health Sciences Administration Council - physical therapy, 1968-1977 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Labor - Health, Education, and Welfare Appropriations Bill - correspondence, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare Appropriations Bill - correspondence, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Series 5: Evaluations, 1939-1987
  - Subseries 5.1: Accreditation and Planning, 1939-1987
    - American Council on Pharmaceutical Education - accreditation reports and correspondence, 1939-1960 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - ACPE Questionnaire - 1980 accreditation, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Progress report from WSU College of Pharmacy to the ACPE, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - ACPE self-study, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - ACPE reports, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Self-study for accreditation review, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Joint committee report and WSU responses - WSU/UW, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Pharmacy education review - response to question 1 - WSU/UW, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Pharmacy education review - response to question 2 - WSU/UW, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Pharmacy education review - response to question 3 - WSU/UW, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Pharmacy education review - response to question 4 - WSU/UW, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Pharmacy education review - response to question 5 - WSU/UW, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Pharmacy education review - response to question 6 - WSU/UW, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Pharmacy education review - response to question 7 - WSU/UW, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Pharmacy education review - response to question 9 - WSU/UW, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Report of the Joint Committee exploring opportunities for the integration of pharmaceutical education at the University of Washington and Washington State University - appendices, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Joint Committee exploring opportunities for the integration of pharmaceutical education at the University of Washington and Washington State University - Final Report, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Report of the Joint Committee exploring opportunities for the integration of pharmaceutical education at the University of Washington and Washington State University - appendices 1/3, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Report of the Joint Committee exploring opportunities for the integration of pharmaceutical education at the University of Washington and Washington State University - appendices 2/3, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Report of the Joint Committee exploring opportunities for the integration of pharmaceutical education at the University of Washington and Washington State University - appendices 3/3, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Internal Review of the College of Pharmacy - announcements, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - WSU Internal Review of the College of Pharmacy - papers and correspondence, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - WSU Internal Review of the College of Pharmacy - newspaper articles and clippings, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - WSU Internal Review of the College of Pharmacy - correspondence, meeting notes, internal reports, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - College of Pharmacy long range academic plans, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Report of the WSU Professional Education Study Council, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Report on the roles and missions of the College of Pharmacy, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - College of Pharmacy long range planning report, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Subseries 5.2: State of Washington Council for Postsecondary Education, 1971-1984
    - State of Washington Council for Postsecondary Education (CPE) staff report on pharmacy education in Washington, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - WSU responses to CPE staff - draft, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - State of Washington CPE report on pharmacy education in Washington - final report, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Papers related to WSU response to CPE report, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - CPE meeting - material for reevaluation of pharmacy manpower, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - CPE support correspondence, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Newspaper articles related to the CPE, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - CPE members and legislators - names and addresses, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Letter to alumni regarding CPE report and WSU responses (included), 1981 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Letters from Allen I. White (AIW) to Larry M. Simonsmeier (LMS) regarding the CPE, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence regarding WSU report to CPE, 1981-07 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - WSU response to CPE report and request for materials, 1981-07-28 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - CPE reports, response, correspondence, 1981-07 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - The Gourman report rating colleges of pharmacy and related correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - CPE reports: Pharmacy education in Washington; Graduate education in Washington, 1981-09 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence and reactions to the supplement to the CPE final report, 1981-09 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Supplement to the CPE report on pharmacy education in Washington, 1981-09 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - CPE staff report - graduate students and the doctor of pharmacy degree, 1981-11-04 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - CPE report: "Graduate Education in Washington: A Review and Evaluation of State Policy" - final report, 1981-11-04 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Other papers related to the CPE, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Papers related to the CPE and the status of pharmacy education at WSU, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - WSU/UW Joint Committee on pharmacy - Pharmacy Education Review, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence with Regent Chakravarti regarding "integration" plan, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Joint Committee on Pharmacy - WSU/UW, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Joint Committee on Pharmacy - WSU/UW, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Joint Committee on Pharmacy - WSU/UW - Manpower, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Joint Committee on Pharmacy - WSU/UW - Manpower, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Joint Committee correspondence and reports - WSU/UW, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Internal actions - WSU College of Pharmacy correspondence and reports to Joint Committee, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Council for Postsecondary Education - State of Washington, 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - WSU College of Pharmacy Graduate Program Review, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - WSU College of Pharmacy Graduate Program Review, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - "Report on Roles and Missions of the College of Pharmacy, Washington State University" and related correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Papers and correspondence related to the Council for Postsecondary Education, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence regarding the CPE Graduate Program Review, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - WSU Graduate School response to CPE recommendation for the termination of programs, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Meeting notes and CPE Graduate Programs Assessment Reports 9 & 10, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence regarding the CPE GPA, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Papers regarding a joint meeting with the University of Washington representatives, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence regarding the CPE Graduate Program Review, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - WSU responses to CPE review of pharmacy education in the State of Washington, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - CPE analysis of the WSU/UW Joint Committee on pharmaceutical education - final report, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence and reports in response to CPE report on pharmaceutical education, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - CPE study correspondence - comments on UW responses, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - CPE study - question 17 - operational costs estimates from other programs, 1973-1977 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - CPE study - questions 19 & 20 - FTE faculty and staff, notes and correspondence, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - CPE study - question 22 - degree conferral numbers 1978-1981, notes and correspondence, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - CPE study - question 23 - elapsed time to degree, notes and correspondence, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - CPE study - question 24 - public service programs, notes and correspondence, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - CPE study - question 28a - information about pharmacy professors and articles regarding the field of pharmacy, notes, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - CPE study - question 28b - retention rates 1953-1979, notes, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - CPE study - question 28e - regional supply, notes and related articles, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence concerning CPE response to Joint Committee Report - notes and correspondence, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - CPE study - comments on four alternatives for pharmacy education - notes and correspondence, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - College of Pharmacy - letters to students and alumni regarding CPE study - notes and correspondence, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Review of CPE staff analysis - memo to John B. Slaughter, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence and notes regarding CPE study, Apr - Dec, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and notes regarding CPE study, Apr - Dec, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - CPE study - Correspondence regarding report from WSU, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - CPE study - report from WSU, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - CPE study - report from WSU - appendices, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Series 6: People, 1917-1993
  - Subseries 6.1: Faculty and Staff, 1951-1993
    - College of Pharmacy faculty, 1985-1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - College of Pharmacy faculty information continued, 1985-1993 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1952-1954 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1954-1956 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1956-1958 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1958-1960 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Pharmacy Faculty-Staff meeting minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Faculty and Faculty Committee meeting minutes, 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Faculty and Faculty Committee meeting minutes, 1984-1986 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Faculty and Faculty Committee meeting minutes and correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Faculty and Faculty Committee meeting minutes and correspondence, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Faculty notices and correspondence, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Faculty notices and correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Faculty notices and correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Meeting of WSU and UW pharmacy faculty - Richland, WA, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 6.2: Graduates and Alumni, 1917-1991
    - College of Pharmacy graduates, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Job placement of pharmacy graduates, 1977-1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - College of Pharmacy alumni - correspondence and newspaper clippings, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - College of Pharmacy mix - papers and correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Alumni donations, 1917-1987 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Lecture notebooks, 1920s (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Series 7: Press coverage, 1896-1989
  - Daily Evergreen articles related to the School of Pharmacy, 1896-1986 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Clippings from WSU Hilltopics, 1975-1989 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings - Idahonian, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings - Pullman Daily News, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper clippings - Spokesman Review, 1978-1988 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper clippings - WSU Bulletin/Calendar, 1986-1989 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - College of Pharmacy "Street Drugs" analysis lab - news releases and newspaper clippings, 1974-1978 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Series 8: Reports, announcements, publications, 1911-1996
  - College of Pharmacy budget allocations, 1948-1958 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - College of Pharmacy annual budgets, 1918-1947 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - College of Pharmacy biennial budgets, 1919-1961 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - College of Pharmacy annual and biennial reports- Enrollment and dept. status, 1913-1951 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - College of Pharmacy finances book, 1942-1952 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - School of Pharmacy announcements, 1896-1926 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - School of Pharmacy announcements, 1927-1961 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - College of Pharmacy announcements, 1962-1977 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Constitution of State College Pharmaceutical Association, 1911 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - WSU Pharmaceutical Echo/Pharmacist publication, 1934-1961 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - WSU pharmacist publication, 1962-1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - WSU pharmacist publication, 1975-1980 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - CougaRx Newsletters, 1982-1996 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Series 9: White, Allen - Personal papers, research, and publications, 1937-1996
  - Papers related to the career of Allen I. White, 1944-1982 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Reports on teaching and activities - Allen I. White, 1940-1977 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Research notes - Allen I. White, 1937-1939 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Research notes - Allen I. White, 1945-1952 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Pharmacy course lab manuals, Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Pharmacy course lab manuals, Undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - "History of the College of Pharmacy" by Allen I. White - unabridged copy, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 6)